What? Then you two...
What about us two?
What are they leaving to you two?
So I want to give back all the benefits that I had to the society.
We started small too and came to where we are today.
It's fun to make money on your own.
Is Jung Hoon a doctor? He will forever earn less money than you.
Looking at the likes of you, you absolutely can't marry him, you useless smartypants!
I don't play games that I can't wait.
You probably put this in your script as well.
I know you married with the bait of being pregnant.
A child? I can give birth to one too.
I haven't been using contraception.
Crazy wench.
- Do you want to stay friends?
- What are you saying?
I'm saying at this point in time we need to settle our relationship.
We can't be like how were were before.
What if I can't be friends?
- Then this is the end.
I have already been to the end.
If you don't want to, forget about it. I won't force it upon you.
Let's do it.
I said, let's do it.
What thing is that your father wil return to society?
Mom!
How could you address me that way in front of your mother, so embarrassingly?!
How much must she look down on me?!
You should have told me mom called you.
Is meeting your mother something to be mad about?
I don't want to show you the low she can be.
Fine, how could I win against you? I was wrong. Even if I didn't do anything wrong.
I was wrong. Is that good enough for you?
Kneel.
Stop. I don't like my man kneeling.
Deul Rae!
Why do you keep calling my name?
That's a little too young for you to carry.
- I'm buying it for Hye Yoon when you guys marry.
- She doesn't know designer labels.
She says she is a designer label. She has a high self esteem.
You're caught again. Do those words mean that your mom looks for designer labels because she has a low self esteem?
No, it's just more realistic. Bread is better than a flower.
Jung Hoon! You are saying that because you don't know women.
When Hye Yoon becomes my daughter in law, she will change.
Meeting arrangement between families of bride and the bridegroom.
I'll go to in front of your house.
Pouter. As if he be could hold out against me without crumbling first?
Mother in law.
- Yes, Mother.
- Hye Yoon, do you have time tomorrow?
I have nothing after school ends.
Then do you want to quickly visit my house?
Yes, mother.
Hye Yoon, I have a lot of expectations and hopes for my daughter-in-law.
Let's have a very close relationship, alright?
- I like it to, mother.
- Alright, I'll see you tomorrow.
You must be feeling good to see your daughter in law.
I like the fact that a woman is coming into our family.
There are some stories only women know. I was lonely in that aspect.
I am a little sad at those words.
Jung Hoon and I have lived as your avatars.
I'm not saying that. I was just jealous of my friends who had daughters.
I wanted to go for a massage and exchanged bags with a daughter.
I'm sorry.
I'm really going to go crazy. I'm falling for you again because you are doing this.
Why don't I hate you?
It's our destiny. Take it in and don't fight it.
Episode 3: A dangerous meeting with my girlfriend's family.
Come in. Were you surprised that I called?
Not at all, Mother.
Let's go in.
Ahjumma, please bring us some mangoes.
Come here.
Sit.
I told you to come to give you this.
Your purse bothered me the last time you came to our house.
Take it out.
When I went to France, I bought this in a Duty Free Shop and never used it.
Because I wanted to give it to my daughter in law.
It's pretty! It is so gorgeous!
It is isn't it? Try it on.
Oh my goodness it is so pretty!
Use this purse when you come to the meeting.
- Yes.
- This is a bag girls want.
I don't know this kind of thing very well.
No wonder your reaction wasn't good. I thought you disliked it.
No, Mother.
Come here.
I have to show her a good reaction.
Why?
Mother, this looks like a celebrity's room!
I saw something like this on Lee Hyori's reality program.
- What size are your feet?
- 245.
Your feet are big. They aren't like mine. Maybe boots will fit you. I wear my boots in a bigger size.
Sit here.
- Try these on.
- Yes.
- It fits!
Stand up!
It looks good on you. Since you are young you look pretty even when wearing high shoes.
- You can have this too.
- Thank you.
You don't feel bad because I wore this once, right?
Of course not!
The reaction right now wasn't that great either.
I have a flat character. If it is something nice I should say so, but I can't really do that.
The reactions I had were the best I could do.
It is not good to be inexperienced in expressing your feelings.
Yes, I will try my best.
I know you were a nurse's aide. As to your background, you aren't better than I am.
Since you entered and wrecked another person's home, it's not like you're honorable.
What are you doing?
What is all of this? Are you having a party?
Why did you come home early all of a sudden?
My constitution isn't what it used to be so I have to only drink on alternating days.
Give me food.
- What are you looking it? I told you to give me food.
- We are going to.
Were going to eat it all.
Take these off.
What are you doing?
What are you thinking?
Mom called and says for us to come to the family marriage meeting for Hae Yoon.
Don't only the immediate family go to the family marriage meetings?
It is enough that we are family. There are no men in our house.
I don't want to go. I don't want to see your mother pushing herself forward.
Still go even if you don't want to see her. I have many things I do even though I don't want to do them.
Food!
What are you saying?
Are you doing this because, I said I will not go to that meeting?
Blood will tell. You're coarse. I absolutely hate coarse people.
Don't forget it's at the hotel at noon. You should order your food.
It will take a long time to clean up the kitchen.
This is me after a shower. Do Hyun likes it the best. I will ignore your advice.
Because it will be a faster for me to make a move before he does.
I love this freedom sensation! and the coffee taste so good.
This is amazing, and this.
Ki Joong, let's not get married and just live like this.
I miss you. Come visit me later, I'll wait for you.
Is it Yuri?
- Yes.
This marriage is lasting longer than I thought it would. Do you love her?
Love? I don't know what love is.
I still can't forget what you said when you were marrying your wife.
I want to protect her, Min Ho. She can not live without me.
She has made me a man.
- Stop saying such things! Did I really say that?
- Yes you did, Hyung.
It's the same anyway. When I lived with my ex-wife now. They are the same.
So stop seeing Yuri or cup.
(Yuri means glass in Korean)
Was that supposed to be a joke? It's not funny at all.
It is funny. Isn't it funny, Do Hyun?
- It is funny.
- Hey! Do Hyun says it is funny too!
It is always you that is the problem.
You should have broken up nicely with Dong Bi if you were going to break up with her.
You were even doused in water.
Why are you bringing that up, so annoyingly?
- Who was he doused in water by?
You didn't know? By Noonim Deul Rae.
- Noonim Deul Rae? Our aunt?
She is not the type to do that.
How much must he have made a person go crazy for a person who wasn't the type to have done that?
But now that I think about it, when I look at my mother in law, my aunt will also have a sleeping ferocious DNA.
I thought my wife was gentle
but sometimes I can see my mother in law in her.
Ki Joong, in marriage you can't only look at the person directly involved.
Because of my mother in law, I don't feel any affection for my wife.
I agree. Do you know why I broke up with Dong Bi?
She never says anything about her family.
She should have told me what kind of
family, because I know who she really is.
It means she has a complex towards her family.
It is tiring living with a woman who has a complex.
You bastards are so full of yourselves. Do you not have complexes?
A person has to have complexes to seem like a human being.
You guys suck.
You have the key, right? You insert the key into the bike's key hole.
Hold the clutch.
Depart.
These disloyal bastards.
Who was it that introduced them? Can't they come out and buy us some dinner?
I'll buy you dinner. They have their family marriage meeting tomorrow, I'm sure they're too busy to come here.
My whole body aches.
Aunt, you have to buy your bike and I'm an unemployed person, let's save money.
Has there been no contact from Min Ho ahjussi?
There was contact just now.
- Ahjussi!
I saw the text late because i was riding a motorcycle.
Hello noonim. I mean... Deul Rae.
Why do you have a pain relief patch on?
She's taking a class to get a bike licence.
Why would you tell him that?
I'd know that just by looking at you, Sis.
- I told you not to call me noonim.
- Alright, Deul Rae.
Let's do this in an american style. Drink my friend, okay?
Deul Rae, sign up for our bike club first. You won't be able to do it alone.
Behave yourself. You are younger than me. Don't act like i'm your friend.
You don't like being friends are being called noona. What do you want to do?
You guys should date.
- Are you crazy?
Our opinion on this is the same. Friend, you should drink.
- Bring me some water.
- Go get it yourself.
What's wrong with you recently?
Wash my feet.
You know tomorrow is the meeting, right?
We're going to pick up my mom and aunt. So, sleep early.
Am i your family's clown?
Tell her to stop using her son-in-law.
You stop showing off because you are a doctor. If you aren't a doctor, is there anything to see?
Is your personality or character great?
Why are you being like this? Have you gone crazy?
I'm still popular. Don't start relaxing. Girls in their twenties still say they like me.
Bastard!
Let go of me!
- Let me at least get hit while knowing the reason.
- Trash!
You met Yuri, didn't you?
Now, you are like a human. You were creepy when you let things like this go before.
I know you look down on me because you know i'm never going to divorce you.
End it with her. It was enough that you met her for three years.
There are many young and pretty women.
Like you said, you are still popular.
You will be able to meet another one.
I don't want to meet anyone else anymore. Just suck it up.
I hate that woman. She's very rude.
She doesn't have the basics. I will never divorce you. Why would I when I went through so much to get married?
I did everything you wanted me to do.
It is hard to live in a marriage like this. You admit that at the least, right?
Yes.
Show yourself off, for my family.
At the meeting, be good son-in-law for my mom.
Let me hear that I married well.
Those kind of words are what sustains me in this marriage.
If we do the ceremony here, can we get some money back?
Do you want to get married here?
- If I say so, will it come true?
- Yes.
- Oh! How are you?
- Take that off.
Take good pictures. It will become a record starting today.
You two stop whimpering.
There's no wedding gift for you
Instead, i will take the pictures and everything.
- This is not right!
- Shut up!
Your parents will sit here.
So bring them here honey, okay?
Don't be like this. You will only get hurt.
Wife.
Stop it.
Why isn't your husband coming in yet? Why isn't he picking up?
He told me he had a surgery. I am guessing he isn't done yet.
Then he should've told us to go there first. We can't be late.
[While waiting for Do Hyun, i heard you have a family meeting today. I guess he will be late.]
- What is it?
- It's nothing.
- Nothing.
- It's probably your husband.
- It probably isn't. Let's go first.
- Hello.
- You already came?
- Were we late?
- Mom and brother in law are not here yet.
- Then we have come first?
- I am sorry.
What is there to be sorry about? There is still time left. We came early.
I feel inferior from the start. They aren't going to be late, right?
How could they when it is such an important meeting? I got a call that they are almost here.
Your skin is better than mine.
My goodness, that is not true! Isn't Hye Yoon so lovely?
In my eyes you are more lovely.
You two... Hye Yoon is the most lovely!
- Shall we take a picture?
- Yes! Hye Yoon, come here and look over there.
I'll take the picture. One, two, three.
We are almost there.
Mother and father are already here! How could you guys do this?
Even if you couldn't come early, you should kept the time!
We are here.
They are too late on a day like this.
Right now, they must be very sorry.
However, they should have been prepared for this at least.
Mom, aunt, get off quickly.
What about you?
- I must park the car.
- You can let a valet do that!
Are you trying to ruin the meeting now?
What happened?
We were only late twenty minutes. Don't overreact.
Is twenty minutes small?
Hello.
You came?
- They came.
- I'm sorry we were late.
We should have met half way. Since we told you to come in our direction, it would have been difficult predicting the traffic.
Thank you for being so understanding.
This is my son in law.
He works at the most famous beauty clinic in Gang Nam.
He made time because it is family business even on a busy Saturday like this.
We put aside all of our morning appointments because it is an important day.
There are some hospitals that you can and others that you cannot. Am i right?
Yes, you are right.
If there is an emergency patient, we can't put them aside.
Is there emergency patients in a plastic surgery hospital?
I'm sorry. I had a patient that after surgery needed my attention.
Hello, I am Hye Yoon's sister's husband.
I heard about you from my child.
There is a colleague meeting next month. I guess I'll probably see you there as well.
I didn't recognize you since I didn't know you, but now it will be different.
I don't go out to colleague meetings much.
Anyways, it is nice to meet you, junior colleague.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Mom, come this way.
Aunt, you should sit next to mom, since you are older than Do Hyun.
My daughter is very polite!
Are you Han Chae Young?
Gong Ki Joong?
I'll finish reading this.
Excuse me, please bring me some coffee.
Today is as happy as the day Jung Hoon was born.
Thank you for giving your lovely daughter to my son.
She is so precious to me that i can eat her own poop.
It's not that Jung Hoon works in a good company. He is just a salary man.
It will be difficult to support their family by his own.
My daughter will be huge help to their family.
I don't encourage for women who have married to work outside of the home.
With the money that husband earns, she can be good wife and mother.
To be honest, you always lack money no matter how much you spend it.
It is because you don't know since you always stay in your house.
Ten out of ten men want women to work.
She had many offers for blind dates, and from men of wealthy families.
Because she became fixated on Jung Hoon, she said she didn't want to meet any more men. That's why we are here.
Were you treated like this in their house?
Thank you for deciding to give us your precious daughter.
You won't regret it if you take her into your family.
Yes.
When should we have the wedding? For us, the faster the better.
It is already November. Let's do it in three months.
That is good. It would get bloody though to find a place for a wedding in three months.
She is crude.
Yes, that is true. It would get bloody.
But must be one place at least.
We have connections. So, don't worry!
If you do the wedding here, they are returning you the money back after one year.
We could do it at this hotel.
That would be too much for our plate.
She never stops talking back.
How would we not be able to find the location? The timing is more of a problem.
Bride's family usually decides the date. Leave that to me.
Yes, please do that.
I will just leave things to you and to my wife.
Let us all have a sip of wine.
Hello.
I was studying MBA at Brown University, but i gave up to start cooking.
Then i went to Paris and i realized what i wanted to do.
- How old were you then?
- 28.
I knew what I wanted when I was in middle school. Having known too early, life is boring.
It's so easy to speak with someone who has the same family standards.
I think I understand what you mean.
You realized that you will live with what you already have and not by getting them working.
Yes, you are right. I want to marry now.
I met many men, but your terms are the best.
I don't like men who work hard. I really hate judges, lawyers and doctors.
- I'll look over it with a positive mind.
- That sounds good.
- I paid.
- No, I'll give you back the money.
Forget it. You're going to spend more money. Save them for that.
Doesn't it bruise your ego after being told such things?
Pardon?
Never mind.
It seems like you don't care one bit. Then you probably will be able to endure in our family.
Hey, honey!
You have been lying to me all this time, right? You were faking that Hye Yoon's mother was treating you nicely, right?
What her mother told you when you went to her store?
Tell me everything.
- It's not like that.
- She is treating you like that?
She couldn't have said that only once today.
- It's not like that!
- You are taking her side even now?
You are not mad?
What is that she has and you don't?
Mom.
You choose Hae Yoon cause she's a teacher and so you can live at her expense?
It is not like that!
A wedding at a hotel is too much for our plate?
Is Hye Yoon really her daughter?
They are too different! It is a twist to the story!
I'm sorry.
Collect your mind!
She came late at the meeting because she is looking down on us.
Honey, who's looking down on us?
That makes no sense.
We just went through something that didn't make any sense.
Why do i have to get treated like that?
She says only her daughter is great. What is wrong with Jung Hoon?
Even Ki Hyun bought a present for the first meeting with her mother-in-law.
She comes without any presents when I gave her a bag?
I'm sorry.
- Do you have anything else to say?
- Yes, I have a little bit more.
Then cry a little bit more.
Did you go in safely?
Where are you?
Home.
Then why didnt you reply to my text?
Why was your family late on a day like today?
Do you think they were late because they wanted to be? They probably had a reason.
The place should've been the middle distance from each others house.
But we did it close to your home.
It takes time to go from Gan Bok to Gang Nam.
That's enough. Let's hang up.
What are you doing?
Why you acting so half-hearted?
I am not in the mood to talk to you on the phone, so let's hang up.
Why aren't you in the mood to be talking with me?
It is because I am a regular salary man who doesn't have a specialized job.
Are you serious? You still talking about that?
I'm very disappointed on you.
- How is mom?
- She is showering.
- I'm sorry.
- What is there to be sorry about?
You were probably hurt too. People live with their own values.
Hye Yoon's mother is just different from us.
- Are you alright?
- I am not alright. Get out. I hate you.
Your mother is comfortless. Did she have to do that in the meeting?
Let's divorce.
I think I gave you enough time to review.
I did review it. You should get married now.
Why do you bring up marriage when we were talking about business?
In order to succeed in the main stream, a man who is married has a higher advantage.
When you open a restaurant as unmarried man, people think that you're playing around.
If I marry, will you invest in my business?
President Han's daughter is a good marriage partner.
I understand.
- Come eat at our house this week.
- Yes.
My dad finished reviewing our marriage.
Same with my family.
When should we meet each other's parents?
Let's do it next week. Let's move quickly if we have already decided.
That sounds good.
Why do you ride this?
You will know why I ride it when you ride it. Do you want to?
- No I don't want to know.
- That's a good attitude.
Hye Yoon.
- Who's call is it?
- Aren't you leaving work?
- Why aren't you picking up?
- I still have work to do.
Do you want to have a drink?
Is something up? I'm worried. Please call me back.
- I'm home.
- What is wrong with you? How much did you drink?
- Mom, I'm sorry.
- What are you sorry about?
For everything!
You are the best, Mom!
Why aren't you replying to me. Already a few days has passed.
- Were you serious about wanting to get married?
- Yes.
I thought you said that just to scare me.
I thought you'd be fine after few days.
She is sending me these and it's not the first time.
I have never been comfortable living with you.
I was just a nurse for you and your wife.
That is your complex!
I thought that too. I was caught up in your logic.
I believed that if I did well, I would be able to be loved by you.
I am tired now.
Divorce is something you have to carefully consider
even more than marriage.
I'm saying that as a divorce man.
Didn't you hear anything of what i just said?
I told you that I didn't have a single day of comfort.
I haven't gone a single day without thinking about divorce.
Alright, I'll do as you like.
You are a very easy man.
Hello.
I don't wonder why you said yes to drink with me.
You're girlfriend was waiting for you.
I'm going. This is my fortune. Who should I drink with?
Why don't you answer my calls?
If I don't answer your calls, there is a reason.
What is that reason?
I needed time to organize my thoughts.
What thoughts?
Let's break up, Hye Yoon.
What did you say?
I'm sorry that you had to come here and hear this.
I was going to call you this weekend.
Why should we break up?
I think I am too lacking for you. Meet a good man.
Don't just say this. Give me a specific reason. Every detail.
Let's not go deeper on that.
It will only heart us more.
This kind of attitude is what is distancing us apart.
Relationships can end because of one small thing.
It's not beacause of world peace or the reunification of South and North.
I don't want to be a coward.
I am not blaming you. I just want to know why you came to think of something so extreme.
Mom cried.
I don't mind to be a coward because i love you.
- But mom is different.
- Why did she cry?
The more we talk, it will become dirty and hurt each other's feelings so let's stop.
No, I need to know. Even if it means it hurts my feelings, I need to know.
So you are saying that you are leaving me because of your mother?
I'm already said it! I think I am too lacking for you.
It's beacause you are just a salary man?
I don't care if we're going to have double income or not.
I don't love you because you are a teacher.
And the same goes for my parents.
But your mother only keeps emphasizing that.
Why does she leave out thanking my parents for raising me well?
My dad thanked your mother a million times for raising you well.
My mom is not good at expressing her feelings.
My mom gave you shoes and a bag before the meeting
- Why didn't you give her any present?
- Was i supposed to do that?
Even Ki Hyun, Ki Joong's sister, bought gifts for her mother-in-law, before the meeting.
Ash, i feel so cheap. Why do i have to tell you those things
What can you gain, if i tell you this?
Sometimes you must let things go.
Next time you meet another man, don't be like this.
How could I meet another man?
I said, how can I meet another man when I love you?
There probably is a better man than a regular salary man.
The woman will eat the man.
The woman has strength and she is fit to be a general.
The man is kind and timid.
Since the woman is suppressing the man, he is unable to succeed.
Are you the woman's family or the man's family.
- Woman's family.
- Let them marry.
Since the man has a good fortune for money, they won't have to worry about money.
Nowadays, there's nothing wrong about controlling someone's husband.
She doesn't want to be controlled by a wealthy man.
When would be a good date?
Let's see.
I also have something I'm curious about.
Ahjumma, your husband will come back soon. Don't worry.
Your husband's girlfriend is very tough, but a charm will fix everything.
Oh my goodness. I haven't married yet. A husband? What are you talking about?
Sis, let's go.
She's a fraud.
I saw your past life for a second.
You suffered too much from a husband in your past life,
that's why you don't like men.
You are right. Even though she hasn't suffered from men, she isnt' interested in them.
I see a man. He is young.
This is not good, though.
- What's your age?
- 50.
Then just marry him!
You are too old!
Be careful of car accidents this year. You might break or fly away.
Deul Ja, she wasn't good fortuneteller.
Let's go and ask someone else.
It's ok. It depends on her luck.
She's always been lucky. She'll be ok.
She isn't going anywhere these days.
I think she has lost her mind. If I ask her what is wrong, she just sleeps.
Is she sleeping already then?
I don't mind to be a coward because i love you.
But mom is different.
I know you aren't sleeping. You know what time it is? Why are you sleeping so early?
I set the date.
It will be January 5th or 12th.
Talk to Jung Hoon's family and let them decide on the date.
Why are you being like this? Is your mind elsewhere?
Just let me be.
Sunday is not too far away. Even if we run right now, we might not be able to get it done in time.
What's wrong?
It's over. He wants us to break up.
His mother cried after the meeting.
You only showed off about me and looked down on Jung Hoon. You hurt his mom's pride.
You must be happy everything turned out the way you wanted.
I don't care if you sent me on blind dates or not.
Just let me be right now.
You were going over board that day.
She's a peculiar woman. I bet she never hear what she doesn't want to hear.
She's from a wealthy family.
Okay, i can understand her. But how can Jung Hoon break up with Hae Yoon?
He is a mama's boy. It's good. If she married a mama's boy, she will suffer forever.
Onni, that's not good.
Jung Hoon was very good at her.
This incident made him spoke words without thinking.
Whatever.
She will marry a better man.
His father seemed nice though.
A son is often like his father. If Hae Yoon marries him, she will live like his mother!
Are you trying to inflame things now?
Yes, mother.
- It's been a while.
- Yes, mother.
I thought we were building up a sense of closeness. Am I wrong?
Why you didn't even contact me after the meeting?
- I'm sorry.
- Is that all you have to say?
For example, you don't want to meet me or come by my house?
Mother, do you have time tomorrow?
I'm sorry, there wasn't an appropriate place to meet in front of the school.
It's alright. It reminds me of the times I went to school.
Do you have more classes?
No, I am in charge of the second graders so I'm done teaching.
- Did your mother decide on a wedding date?
- Yes.
I know it's pointless right now, but on the day we had the meeting...
Yes.
Does your mother not like Jung Hoon?
- I was displeased that day.
- I'm sorry.
There were many girls who said liked Jung Hoon too.
But why i wasn't picky on selecting my daughter-in-law?
Because i saw one thing.
A woman who wants to be with my son.
What's wrong?
Is what I am saying harsh?
No, mother.
Something bad came on my mind.
That's all.
- What?
- I don't want to tell you.
If I tell you, I am afraid it will actually come true.
Stop it. You have to go back to work.
Leave it.
Get a hold of yourself and go back to work.
It's been ten minutes since lunch time was over.
Hey! You have to at least pay!
I'm sorry, it's because the article was published that way. The toy with the issue isn't our company's.
I'm sorry.
I will request correction on the news report.
- And...
- Who will read that?
You acting very strange lately.
Is everything allright?
You're smelling alcohol.
Did you drink during the day?
How much did you drink for the smell to still linger?
-I'm sorry
-Are you having problems with your girlfriend?
What's wrong? You're drinking for couple days now.
You didn't even take off your sweaty clothes, so dirty. I met Hye Yoon earlier and she's acting strangely too.
Have you decided to be strange as a group?
Hey, why aren't you saying anything? I asked you why you aren't saying anything.
Why are you being like this. What's wrong?
- We broke up.
- You broke up with Hye Yoon?
- Yes.
- Why?
Because you cried, Mom. I can handle it if people are insulting me. But i can't if you are.
Jung Hoon!
So don't meet Hye Yoon ever again.
We are over.
Everything is falling into place.
So, why he's drinking everyday and Hae Yoon is acting weird?
- He said they broke up.
- They broke up?
It looks like because of me, he told Hye Yoon they should break up.
My mind tells me that this is not good.
But my heart knows that i've raised my son well.
I should have told my mother in law that we broke up.
I couldn't do it because I was afraid it would come true.
How could he say we should break up? How could he do this to me?
That is what the victim says. You were always the assailant.
- It's good for the side of Jung Hoon's.
- Are you really my friend?
You guys are both tormenting me. You call him! You can call Jung Hoon!
Tell him you guys should meet and that you are sorry.
- Did my mom do so wrong?
- But she wasn't right also.
If it was me, I would have been mad too.
- Hit me once.
- Why are you being like this?
Hit me once so I get a hold of myself.
Why i'm thinking the man who he broke up with me because he hates me?
What are you doing? You are crazy!
Hit me once so that I get a hold of myself and forget that bastard.
- Don't regret it.
- I won't
Hye Yoon, are you alright?
- Let's see.
- It's okay.
- What are you guys doing this late in the night?
- I'm going to go.
Sleep over.
What's wrong with your face? Who hit you? Who is the bastard?
It's alright. Don't make a fuss.
Did Jung Hoon hit you? Did you meet him?
You are hopeless.
Do you know how he treated me?
If I told him that I wanted a moon, he would give me anything that would look like a moon.
Have you done that for me? I lost a man like that because of you.
What did I do for her to resent me?
Then who did she get hit by? You would know.
I hit her.
Mother, I didn't hit her because I wanted to. She kept telling me to hit her. I am not a pervert.
She wants to forget the pain with pain.
Go home.
You waited a long time, right? You should have called before you came.
You keep this studio apartment.
It sounds like your last farewell.
Marrying to an adulterer once is enough.
I know you are doing this because you are too young and can't distinguish heaven and earth.
You have lots of opportunities because you are pretty and young.
Did she tell you to break up with me?
I'm not a person to act upon other's orders.
I don't do the things I don't want to do.
You shouldn't have touched my wife.
- Oppa!
- Don't cry. I'm a player.
I'm not a man that will change with tears.
Buy leather pants too. It wil become a set.
Do that. Buy it when your husband tells you he will buy.
- He is not my husband.
- Then are you two siblings?
It's not like that. Who do you think is older?
- Boss.
- Hey!
How much is it for all of this?
I'll tell you with the deduction of the five hundred dollar coupon from the purchase of the bike.
You must be so happy that he thinks i'm your husband.
You are calling me noonim again. Can you really not improve even if I keep telling you?
If you are dumb, you suffer for eternity no matter if you are a child or an adult.
I like you, noonim.
I mean i like the fact that i'm calling her noonim.
Let's suppress it since I have a favor to ask of you.
What's the favor?
This the favor I am asking.
You want me to store this in my house?
Due to the situation, I can't bring it to my house.
If I accept the favor, what would you do for me?
- You can call me noonim.
- That's not big deal.
Letting someone younger call me noonim, means i'm giving up some part of my life.
- What are you giving up?
- Marriage.
Noona, even if it hadn't been me, you would have to give that up.
Everyone else has given up too. Marriage at fifty?
- You're not even married.
- Are you going to do me the favor or not?
What's your reason for going to this extent to ride the bike?
Because I feel like I would die of boredom.
For fifty years now my life has been housework, school and work.
I feel that i will die with nothing in my 60s or 70s.
Before I die, I want to break away.
You pass. If that is your reason, I'll accept your favor noona.
Noona! I really hate it.
- Sleep on the bed with me.
- It's too crammed to sleep.
Sang Jin here. Long time no see. Let's have a lunch sometime.
What is this?
Who is it?
- It's Sang Ji!
- Why did he text me?
Wouldn't it mean he still has feelings?
- I hate him.
- Don't delete it!
Why?
I told you he is doing well. The law firm that this oppa is going to isn't a place anyone can go to.
Why does that matter to me?
Living in this world, it is good to know at least one doctor and lawyer.
- Who is this?
- Oppa, it's Dong Bi.
It's you, Dong Bi. You saw Hye Yoon's facebook, right?
- You guys still stick together.
- Hye Yoon!
Why you did that Deul Ja?
I can't sleep. I can't sleep unless I drink alcohol.
My head hurts too much. Hye Yoon.
What are you doing not coming in?
I reserved this place for you.
Open it.
I was surprised.
Since i'm working on a toy company, i made that by myself.
Why did you make it?
You could just brought me one from your company.
It was discontinued.
It's my heart. My heart beats whenever i see you.
I'm getting goose bumps.
Jung Hoon loves Hye Yoon!
I think love is forever. It is the person that changes, not love.
That was so romantic! Did you think it by yourself?
Could you please not change the mood and listen?
Come and sit.
How did he find that place?
That oppa still has a good sense for seducing women.
It's been a long time.
Hye Yoon, you became more pretty.
- Don't you see me?
- I see you.
How could you not call me even once? You really are venomous.
This is Jun Sang Jin.
Of course, please speak.
Ofcourse you can sue him. There's a judicial precedent about that, too.
In America is more easy to file for bankrupt, but i guess it will be possible in Korea, too.
Yes, I'll see you later.
Are you a specialized as a divorce lawyer?
Usually i take every case.
In such a big law firm, they don't divide up the specialties?
That was a very long time ago. Now i'm working by my own.
Why? Isn't a big law firm better?
I got fired. Let's eat.
Yes.
Just a second.
- I'll just go.
- Why?
This was a place I came with Jung Hoon.
Yes, please speak.
- Are you crazy?
- Sorry...
What are you doing not going in?
Didn't you come here to meet Jung Hoon?
Jung Hoon can't be here right now. I guess you have no time since you are the CEO.
- Then why are you here at this time?
- It's a school anniversary.
If it's a school anniversary and you aren't meeting Jung Hoon, why are you here? Did you come to meet me?
A poem says that "habits can be safe".
It's a habit. Go in.
Why is she being like that?
Hye Yoon.
Hye Yoon just came and went. Weren't you two planning to meet?
She is weird these days. She is different from normal. She has her mind elsewhere.
She almost got hit by my bike.
And she was speaking about a poem and habits or something.
Let's talk.
Is it true you broke up with Hye Yoon?
Yes.
- You told Hye Yoon?
- Yes.
Was she accepting?
She would have to accept it.
Marriage is between two female and male adults.
I'm affraid that you will carry the feeling of your mother into your marriage.
I'm sorry.
Keep it in mind. The main focus in marriage is you and Hye Yoon.
Other people are just surrounding people.
Instead of being swayed by the surrounding people, I would like it for you two to make the best possible decision for yourselves.
Why you returning so late at night?
- Why are you lying there?
- Because I am tired.
You're not worry about Hae Yoon?
She looks so depressed.
Do you know what she said earlier? She says she will shave her hair and go into a temple.
What should I do?
You said Dong Bi is Jung Hoon's friend. Tell Dong Bi to gently coax him.
I want to do it, but if they get back together...
then i have to do whatever his family wants.
What? You think you can be slave to someone's pleasure?
It's best if you call his mother and apologize about that day.
Apologize for what?